<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCity</string>
    <string name="kone_cafe">Kone Café</string>
    <string name="kone_cafe_addr">295 Kham Thien Street, Tho Quan Ward, Dong Da District</string>
    <string name="kone_cafe_desc">Kone Cafe is located at the Kham Thien - O Cho Dua Intersection, which is a hub of cafes and restaurants. The interior is designed with minimalism in mind, with white and brown as the main colors. It is well worth it to sip a cup of coffee or black macchiato while smelling the pleasant aromas of tea and oils in a relaxing and homey atmosphere! Despite having a limited number of drinks, this Hanoi coffee shop focuses on authenticity and quality. Some unique beverages available are caramel tea macchiato, yogurt coffee, hazelnut macchiato, peach mojito, and strawberry mojito.</string>
    <string name="giang_coffee">Giang Coffee</string>
    <string name="giang_coffee_addr">39 Nguyen Huu Huan Street, Ly Thai To Ward, Hoan Kiem District</string>
    <string name="giang_coffee_desc">In Hanoi, there are many shops selling egg coffee, and the most famous one is Giang Coffee. The egg coffee here is very fragrant, smooth, and rich. It consists of 2 egg cream and black coffee, blended together perfectly to create a unique coffee.\n\nCafe Giang was founded in 1940, when a talented chef named Giang of the Metropole Hotel was looking for an alternative to cow\'s milk (a luxury ingredient at that time) to make cappuccino. His creativity had brought Hanoi a specialty that any visitor to Hanoi today must try: egg coffee.</string>
    <string name="lofita">Lofita - Paris Dream</string>
    <string name="lofita_addr">9-10th floors, 338 Pho Hue Street, Le Dai Hanh Ward, Hai Ba Trung District</string>
    <string name="lofita_desc">Head to Pho Hue, one of the busiest streets in downtown Hanoi, and visit Lofita - Paris Dream, a marvelous cafe in authentic Western style. This is a branch of Lofita, a well-known coffee chain in Northern Vietnam. Situated on the 9th and 10th floors of a tall building, from the balconies, you can contemplate the whole view of the city. Aside from its unique and modern design, what draws young people here is the menu of healthy and trendy refreshments, from milk tea, cappuccino to latte.</string>
    <string name="duong">Duong’s Restaurant</string>
    <string name="duong_addr">27 Ngo Huyen Street, Hoan Kiem District, Hanoi, Vietnam.</string>
    <string name="duong_desc">Located in the heart of Hanoi Old Quarter, Duong’s Restaurant is a hidden gem that offers an unforgettable culinary experience. This cozy restaurant features a charming Vietnamese ambiance and a menu that highlights the flavors and traditions of local cuisine. Their signature dishes, such as the aromatic Pho and the tender Grilled Fish with Turmeric, are a must-try for any food enthusiast. With attentive service and affordable prices, Duong’s Restaurant is a beloved spot among both locals and tourists alike.</string>
    <string name="l_essence_de_cuisine">L’essence De Cuisine</string>
    <string name="l_essence_de_cuisine_addr">99 Hang Gai, Hoan Kiem District, Hanoi, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="l_essence_de_cuisine_desc">For those craving a taste of French cuisine in the heart of Hanoi, L’essence De Cuisine is the perfect choice. This elegant restaurant combines classic French flavors with a modern twist, creating a dining experience that is both sophisticated and delightful. From the rich Foie Gras to the decadent Beef Bourguignon, each dish at L’essence De Cuisine is thoughtfully curated and expertly executed. With its chic ambiance and impeccable service, this restaurant is a true culinary destination.</string>
    <string name="era">Era Restaurant</string>
    <string name="era_addr">48 Ma May Street, Hoan Kiem District, Hanoi, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="era_desc">Located on Ma May street in the heart of the Old Quarter, Era Restaurant is known for its cozy atmosphere and delectable Vietnamese dishes. This family-owned restaurant takes pride in serving authentic cuisine that showcases the rich flavors of Vietnam. From hearty noodle soups to fragrant rice dishes, Era Restaurant offers a culinary journey that will transport you to the vibrant streets of Hanoi.</string>
    <string name="thu_le">Thu Le Park</string>
    <string name="thu_le_addr">Kim Ma Street, Cau Giay District, Hanoi.</string>
    <string name="thu_le_desc">"Thu Le Park, also known as Hanoi Zoo, is a green space with flourishing green trees and flowers, located in Ngoc Khanh Ward, Ba Dinh District, only 5 kilometers to the Northwest of the city center. \n\nFirst constructed on May 19, 1975, Thu Le Park then opened to the public two years later. It is a spacious park spread over a 29-hectare area, with a 6-hectare lake nestled inside. There is a stretch of land with a shape that appears like a drop of tear, which is the origin of the name “Thủ Lệ”, which means to “embrace the tear”. \n\nToday, Thu Le Park is not only home to numerous different animals, but also offers a space for recreation and entertainment for every age group. "</string>
    <string name="thong_nhat">Thong Nhat Park</string>
    <string name="thong_nhat_addr">354A Le Duan Street, Phuong Lien, Dong Da Ward, Hanoi.</string>
    <string name="thong_nhat_desc">Thong Nhat Park is another big park in Hanoi. Though having Bay Mau Lake located in the center, bordering to four mains streets, the park is very tranquil and airy. Thong Nhat park has always been the ideal destination for relaxation, entertainment, group activities, outdoor education or even fairs.\n\nThere is a peaceful and serene Hoa Binh island in the middle of Bay Mau lake, and there are many areas for growing flowers and ornamental plants, various interesting games for children such as ferris wheel, mirror house, rowing boat, etc. Particularly on holidays, this park is also the venue for the Spring Flower Fair with thousands of beautiful and fragrant flowers.</string>
    <string name="indira_gandhi">Indira Gandhi Park</string>
    <string name="indira_gandhi_addr">16B Lang Ha, Ba Dinh District, Hanoi.</string>
    <string name="indira_gandhi_desc">Indira Park is located just opposite the National Cinema Center. It sounds strange because the park takes the name of India’s first female Prime Minister – Indira Gandhi to celebrate the 50th anniversary of the liberation day of Hanoi capital. The statue turns to the North, and its main gate is on Lang Ha Street looking spectacular and solemn.\n\nThis park embraces Thanh Cong lake, whose water was purified and filtereclean. This lake also has a magnificent fountain  with greenery system forming clean playing areas and beautiful scenery.</string>
    <string name="lotte">Lotte Center Hanoi</string>
    <string name="lotte_addr">54 P. Liễu Giai, Ngọc Khánh, Ba Đình, Hà Nội 117000, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="lotte_desc">Lotte Center Hanoi offers a broad range of approximately 250 fashion and lifestyle brands. This 1-stop shopping spot also offers enough entertainment and dining possibilities that you could easily spend a half-day here. The 65-storey building can be reached from Hoan Kiem Lake by car in around 20 minutes. The high-rise building that houses the Lotte Shopping Center Hanoi is also home to a hypermarket, a hotel, residential apartments, restaurants, a gym, a spa and the city’s finest observation deck.</string>
    <string name="trang_tien">Trang Tien Plaza</string>
    <string name="trang_tien_addr">24 Hai Bà Trưng, Tràng Tiền, Hoàn Kiếm, Hà Nội 100000, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="trang_tien_desc">Trang Tien Plaza is a favourite shopping spot among Hanoi’s rich and famous and is a 5-minute walk from Hoan Kiem Lake and the French Quarter. The 5-storey shopping mall houses luxury fashion brands such as Cartier, Burberry, Dior, Zegna, BVLGARI, and Louis Vuitton on the ground floor, while electronics and home décor outlets can be found on the upper levels. There’s also a supermarket on the 4th floor, which stocks fresh produce and an array of imported goods. Trang Tien Plaza hosts excellent international restaurants with a variety of regional cuisine and plenty of fast-food chains, including Dunkin Donuts, Lotteria, and Paris Baguette.</string>
    <string name="royal">Vincom Mega Mall Royal City</string>
    <string name="royal_addr">Vinhomes Royal City, 72A-Đ. Nguyễn Trãi, Thượng Đình, Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="royal_desc">A massive underground shopping mall, Vincom Mega Mall Royal City boasts 800 retail outlets, a massive hypermarket, as well as numerous outdoor and indoor recreational facilities in Hanoi’s Thanh Xuan District. Featuring an elegant all-white interior design, the shopping mall houses an indoor ice-skating rink, cinema, and a food-and-beverage street with more than 200 international and local restaurants. Vincom Mega Mall Royal City is also home to the biggest rainforest-themed indoor water park in Southeast Asia, where visitors of all ages can enjoy 6 complexes of water slides, wave pools, concave sliding tubes, and water games.</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back button</string>
    <string name="coffee">Coffee shops</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="mall">Shopping Centers</string>
</resources>